

# IZADORA CURY PIERETTE

JUNIOR DEVELOPER

• CAMPO GRANDE, 79063-100, BRASIL

**4** 67984098786

#### °DETAILS °

Street Name: Francisco Aguiar
Pimenta, 1289, Neighborhood
Name: Universitário
Campo Grande, 79063-100
Brasil
67984098786
ipierette2@gmail.com

Date / Place of birth 12/22/2022 Campo Grande

> Nationality Brazilian

° SKILLS °

**CSS** 

HTML

JavaScript

Unity

°LANGUAGES °

English

Spanish

## ° LINKS °



## PROFILE

Lawyer with a postgraduate degree in Public Law, with over 9 years of experience leading the legal sector of Public Administration.

Afer 3 years working part time as Senior Moderator for a mobile application (under NDA regime) and the close contact with problems and challenges in Application Development and Customer Service, the situation rekindled my desire to work with Technology what culminated in the beginning of my studies in Web Development Front and Back end.

Non-Experienced Soft are Developer Equipped with a diverse and promising skill-set. Proficient in various platforms, languages, and embedded systems. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

## EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Lawyer at Secretaria Municipal de Políticas para a Mulher, Campo Grande

November 2014 — January 2016

Assistance in the administrative sector of the Secretariat of Policies for Women – SEMMU. (General notions of e-Doc. and e-Diary; review of public purchases procedures and design build for banners, folders and other).

Lawyer at Procuradoria Geral do Município de Campo Grande, Campo Grande April 2016 — April 2017

Assistance in the Tax Affairs Coordination of the Attorney General's Office of the Municipality of Campo Grande-MS, where beside other things i updated, created or edited all the models of texts currently used for manifestation in tax execution processes and also prepared the Apostille on the Tax Execution Procedure for assist the advisors and trainees of this Coordination, in the manifestation in Tax Enforcement processes, containing introductory and specific theoretical questions, as well as recently used models of manifestations.

Lawyer at Subsecretária de Políticas para Mulher, Campo Grande

July 2017 — Present

Head of Legal Counsel at the Undersecretariat of Public Policies for Women in Campo Grande-MS, preparing demonstrations, setting up and managing public procurement processes, creating dsigns for promotional materials.

Senior Moderator at Non-disclosure agreement, Home Office from Campo Grande July 2019 - Present

Managing a team of Moderators and ensuring that everyone is fulfilling their duties according to the interests of the company, reporting and managing situations involving bugs and translation errors in the application and in the company's social media, providing full service to users.

## EDUCATION

Postgraduate Degree in Public Law at Damásio Educacional, Campo Grande Graduation, Universidade Descomplica, Campo Grande

Conducting Course on Analysis and Development of EAD Systems - Universidade Descomplica.

Doing other online courses, focused on Full stack Development of WEB Front and Back end.